<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string-array name="PlacesName">
        <item>The Imperial Palace</item>
        <item>National Art Center</item>
        <item>National Museum of nature and science</item>
        <item>The Senso-ji Temple</item>
        <item>The SkyTree Tower</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ParksName">
        <item>Todoroki Valley</item>
        <item>Chichibu-Tama-Kai National Park</item>
        <item>Hama Rikyu</item>
        <item>Yoyogi Park</item>
        <item>Shinjuku Gyoen</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RestaurantName">
        <item>Ginza Kojyu</item>
        <item>Ishikawa</item>
        <item>L’Effervescence</item>
        <item>Sukiyabashi Jiro</item>
        <item>Sushi Yoshitake</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="PlacesDescription">
        <item>The Tokyo Imperial Palace (皇居, Kōkyo, literally Imperial Residence) is the usual
            residence of the Emperor of Japan.It is a large park-like area located in the Chiyoda
            district of the Chiyoda ward of Tokyo and contains several buildings including the main
            palace (宮殿, Kyūden), some residences of the Imperial Family, an archive, museums and
            administrative offices. Working hours: 9am - 2pm</item>
        <item>The National Art Center (国立新美術館, Kokuritsu Shin-Bijutsukan) (NACT) is a museum in
            Roppongi, Minato, Tokyo, Japan. A joint project of the Agency for Cultural Affairs and
            the National Museums Independent Administrative Institution, it stands on a site formerly
            occupied by a research facility of the University of Tokyo. The building has been designed
            by Kisho Kurokawa. Working hours: 10am - 6pm</item>
        <item>The National Museum of Nature and Science (国立科学博物館, Kokuritsu Kagaku Hakubutsukan)
            is in the northeast corner of Ueno Park in Tokyo. Opened in 1871, it has had several names,
            including Ministry of Education Museum, Tokyo Museum, Tokyo Science Museum, the National
            Science Museum of Japan, and the National Museum of Nature and Science as of 2007. Working hours: 7am - 5pm</item>
        <item>Sensō-ji (金龍山浅草寺, Kinryū-zan Sensō-ji) is an ancient Buddhist temple located in
            Asakusa, Tokyo, Japan. It is Tokyo oldest temple, and one of its most significant.
            Formerly associated with the Tendai sect of Buddhism, it became independent after World
            War II. Adjacent to the temple is a five-story pagoda, the Asakusa Shinto shrine, as
            well as many shops with traditional goods in the Nakamise-dōri. Working hours: 6am - 5pm</item>
        <item>Tokyo Skytree (東京スカイツリー, Tōkyō Sukaitsurī, stylized TOKYO SKYTREE) is a broadcasting
            and observation tower in Sumida, Tokyo. It became the tallest structure in Japan in 2010
            and reached its full height of 634.0 meters (2,080 ft) in March 2011, making it the tallest
            tower in the world, displacing the Canton Tower, and the second tallest structure in the
            world after the Burj Khalifa (829.8 m/2,722 ft). Working hours: 9am - 9pm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ParksDescription">
        <item>The only valley in the city, it comprises a roughly one-kilometer walking trail that
            winds along lazily next to the Yazawa River. As soon as you descend into the narrow ravine,
            you’ll notice the air become cooler and the atmosphere more tranquil. Todoroki is rarely
            busy, making it the perfect place to escape the city (while still being in it). Benches
            are dotted along the route, where you can sit and relax, have lunch, or read a book while
            listening to the gentle sound of the river. Working hours: 24/7</item>
        <item>Chichibu-Tama-Kai National Park is a national park in Japan at the intersection of
            Saitama, Yamanashi, Nagano and Tokyo Prefectures.With eight peaks over 2000 m scattered
            over 1250 km², there are numerous hiking trails and ancient shrines. The best known landmarks
            are Mount Mitsumine, home to the 2000-year-old Mitsumine Shrine and Mount Mitake, with
            the Musashi-Mitake Shrine. The park has sources of major rivers such as the Arakawa River,
            Shinano River, Tama River, and Fuefuki River (Fuji River). Working hours: 4am - 6pm</item>
        <item>Hamarikyu Gardens is a public park in Chūō ward, Tokyo, Japan. Located at the mouth of
            the Sumida River, it was opened to the public on April 1, 1946. A landscaped garden of
            250,216 m² includes Shio-iri Pond, and the park is surrounded by a seawater moat filled
            by Tokyo Bay. It was remodeled as a public park on the site of a villa belonging to the
            ruling Tokugawa family in the 17th century. Working hours: 9am - 5pm</item>
        <item>The park is a popular Tokyo destination. On Sundays, it is especially busy when it is
            used as a gathering place for Japanese rock music fans, jugglers, comedians, martial arts
            clubs, cosplayers and other subculture and hobby groups.[1] In spring, thousands of people
            visit the park to enjoy the cherry blossom during hanami. The landscaped park has picnic
            areas, bike paths, cycle rentals and public sport courts. Working hours: 24/7</item>
        <item>Shinjuku Gyo-en (新宿御苑) is a large park and garden in Shinjuku and Shibuya, Tokyo,
            Japan. It was originally a residence of the Naitō family in the Edo period. Afterwards,
            it became a garden under the management of the Imperial Household Agency of Japan. It is
            now a national park under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of the Environment. Working hours: 9am - 4pm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RestaurantDescription">
        <item>Ginza Kojyu is one of the best places in Tokyo to experience kaiseki dining. The cozy
            interior creates the feeling of a meal prepared in someone’s home, with the servers
            describing each dish as diners watch it being prepared at the counter. The seasonal menu
            emphasises traditional Japanese cuisine, along with a few experimental dishes. The restaurant
            is quite small and relatively affordable, so it’s best to reserve a table in advance.
            Working hours: 12am - 21pm</item>
        <item>Ishikawa offers an all-round intimate dining experience, from the attentive staff who
            help customers find their way to the restaurant’s hidden alleyway location to the chef
            who typically comes around to tables ensuring all diners are satisfied. Guests are presented
            with several fixed courses which typically consist of an appetiser, soup, sashimi, and a
            grilled main. Seating is offered in elegant private dining areas or along the cypress-wood
            counter with a view of Chef Hideki Ishikawa at work. The kimono-clad servers are a nod
            to the neighbourhood’s history as a prominent geisha district. Working hours: 5pm - 9pm</item>
        <item>L’Effervescence, a French term that translates to ‘bubbles’, ‘that which makes people
            gather’, or ‘lively’ depending on the context, befits this restaurant perfectly. The dishes
            here exude a touch of playfulness, such as its upscale take on the McDonald’s takeaway
            apple pie made with wild boar or sage and matutake mushrooms, served in a red takeaway
            box. The restaurant is known for its exquisite desserts, including its caramelized apple
            and kuromoji ice cream served with muesli. The setting in an elegant Japanese style, and
            an excellent menu of French wines complement the innovative menu. Working hours: 12am - 12pm</item>
        <item>After winning three stars from the Michelin Guide, Sukiyabashi Jiro has become one of
            the most famous sushi restaurants in the world. The chef and owner, Jiro Ono, was the
            star of David Gelb’s 2011 documentary, ‘Jiro Dreams of Sushi’, which put his tiny restaurant
            firmly on the traveller’s map. It’s pretty no-frills, with a simple sushi bar only sitting
            a few guests, who are served a set menu of beautifully prepared and selected sushi. Anyone
            who saw the documentary will recognise Jiro and his team’s attention to detail, from choosing
            the fish in the early hours, to massaging an octopus for a whole morning. Working hours: 12am - 8pm</item>
        <item>Having earned three stars from Michelin, sushi chef Masahiro Yoshitake has put his
            sushi restaurant, Sushi Yoshitake , on the map. Expect inventive interpretations of
            classic sushi dishes. Yoshitake is particularly famous for his abalone, accompanied with
            a special sauce made from abalone liver, uni and oyster. Serving small plates in the
            omakase style in front of the clientele, Toshitake only takes reservations for two sittings
            each night and demand is high, so be sure to call far in advance for your table. Working hours: 6pm - 11pm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="PlacesAddress">
        <item>1-1 Chiyoda, Chiyoda City, Tokyo 100-8111</item>
        <item> 7-22-2 Roppongi Minato-ku Tokyo 106-8558</item>
        <item>7-20 Uenokoen, Taito, Tokyo 110-8718</item>
        <item>2 Chome-3-1 Asakusa, Taito, Tokyo 111-0032</item>
        <item>1 Chome-1-2 Oshiage, Sumida, Tokyo 131-0045</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ParksAddress">
        <item>22, 1 Chome, Todoroki Setagaya City, Tokyo, 158-0082</item>
        <item>Tokura Akiruno, Tokyo, 190-0173</item>
        <item>Hama Rikyu, 1-1 Hamarikyuteien, Chuo, Tokyo</item>
        <item>1 2, Yoyogikamizonochō Shibuya City, Tokyo, 151-0052</item>
        <item>Shinjuku Gyoen, 11 Naitomachi, Shinjuku, Tokyo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RestaurantAddress">
        <item>Ginza Kojyu, Carioca Bldg. 4fl., 5 Chome-4-8 Ginza, Chuo, Tokyo</item>
        <item>Ishikawa, 162-0825, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo Kagurazaka 5-37 Takamura Building 1F -JR Sobu, Tokyo</item>
        <item>L’Effervescence, 2-26-4 Nishiazabu, Minato, Tokyo</item>
        <item>15 2, 4-chōme, Ginza Chuo City, Tokyo, 104-0061</item>
        <item>Sushi Yoshitake, 銀座8-7-19, Chūō, 東京都 〒104-0061</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="PlacesPhone">
        <item>+81 3-3213-1111</item>
        <item>+81 3-5777-8600</item>
        <item>+81 3-5777-8600</item>
        <item>+81 3-3842-0181</item>
        <item>+81 570-550-634</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ParksPhone">
        <item>+81 3-3704-4972</item>
        <item>+81 3-3641-5892</item>
        <item>+81 3-3541-0200</item>
        <item>+81 3-3469-6081</item>
        <item>+81 3-3350-0151</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RestaurantPhone">
        <item>+81 3-6215-9544</item>
        <item>+81 3-5225-0173</item>
        <item>+81 3-5766-9500</item>
        <item>+81 3 3535-3600</item>
        <item>+81 3-6253-7331</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>